So you've got a pretty sweet looking control, but what about
users who can't see the shiny hotness? Accessibility is a key consideration
when building apps and particularly when you're creating new views. You
can start by adding a content description, as you would for every
other view in your layout, to ensure that they are all
accessible. But what about views like our wind speed, and direction gauge,
where the content isn't static? Knowing you're looking at a wind
gauge isn't very useful if you don't know what the speed and
direction it's displaying are. Well, there are couple
of options here. For generic views, which don't control
their own values, this simplest alternative is to
set the content description within your app at runtime.
An even more robust solution is to send
an accessibility event from within your view. Whenever the
visual content has been modified. Then override the dispatch
populate accessibility event, and then the current control's visual
value, the accessibility event. Go ahead and add accessibility handlers
to your view and then click here when you're done.